A Guide to the Rockefeller Archive Center photographs FA095
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Archive Center photographs
1974-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
FA095
0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Appraisal
As received.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised entirely of photographs which document the history of the Rockefeller Archive Center.
Photographs; Archives
- Rockefeller Archive Center, 1974-1987; 1038; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 14, Folder 182)
    Scope and Contents note
    Archives, exteriors, Libraries, Collections, RAC, Staff,
  - Archival Projects (Box 14, Folder 183)
    Documents, conservation, archives
  - RAC - Construction, Oversized, panoramic. (Box 1)
  - Construction - Negatives by Roll (1-14) (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Construction - Architectual Plans (Box 14, Folder 185)
    Archives
  - RAC - Hillcrest, Oversized, panoramic. (Box 1)
  - Archive Center Construction - July-November 1974 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    Archives, Construction, Hillcrest
  - Archive Center Construction - November 1974-June 1975 (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - Archive Center Construction (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - Costume Collection (Box 14, Folder 189)
    Costumes, Clothing, RAC Collections
  - Furnishings (Box 14, Folder 190)
    Textiles, furnishings, RAC Collections, Interiors, Decorations, Art, Accessories
  - Furnishings - Office - JDR Jr (Box 14, Folder 191)
    Furniture, Decoration, accessories, Offices
  - Computers in Small and Medium Archives - Conference, 1987 December 9 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    Conferences, Archives, Meetings, Hillcrest
  - Computers in Small and Medium Archives - Conference, 1987 December 9 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    Archives, Hillcrest, meetings, conferences,
  - Computers in Small and Medium Archives - Conference - Exhibit - December 9, 1987, 1987 December 9 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    Exhibitions, Archives, Conferences, Meetings
  - Staff and Rooms, 1987 December 10 (Box 15, Folder 195)